billmatrix.com 2006-04-14

# BillMatrix - The payment experts.™

At BillMatrix, we are committed to protecting your privacy online. Our goal is to safeguard any personal information you provide to us. Personal information includes data that reasonably can be used to identify or describe an individual, such as name, address, phone number, and e-mail address. To meet this goal we will:

  * notify you when our website is collecting personal information; 
  * inform you on what information is being collected; 
  * obtain your permission if we seek to use your personal information in a way other than specified when it was collected; 
  * take reasonable steps to protect your information; and 
  * give you an opportunity to review and update your personal information. 

Commitment to Online Security   
BillMatrix uses a variety of administrative and technical security measures to maintain the safety of your information. Personal information is contained behind a secured network that is designed to be accessible only by a limited number of employees. 

Personal Information that BillMatrix May Collect Online   
BillMatrix typically collects the following types of personal information: names, companies, titles, postal and e-mail addresses, phone numbers and type of informational literature you request.

Children's Privacy   
BillMatrix does not knowingly collect or maintain information from children under the age of 13, and no part of our site is structured to attract anyone under the age of 13. If we learn that we have personal information on a child under the age of 13, we will delete that information from our systems.

How BillMatrix May Use Personal Information Collected Online   
BillMatrix will not use your personal information other than for the purpose for which it was submitted without your consent. We typically use personal information to respond to informational literature requests and to organize meetings. At any time you can add or remove your name from our mailing list by contacting us at [info@billmatrix.com](mailto:info@billmatrix.com). Any e-mail communication or newsletter also has instructions on how to unsubscribe.

How Your Information May Be Shared   
BillMatrix will not sell or distribute your personal information without your consent, provided that we may transfer such information in connection with the sale of our business. We may provide aggregate statistics about our customers, sales and related site information to outside parties interested in demographics, but no personally identifiable information or company data will ever be shared for such purposes. We may be required to share information in connection with the enforcement of laws or regulation or other legal action or in connection with violations of our Terms of Use.

Accuracy of Your Personal Information   
If your personal information changes or you would like to review the personal information we may have on file, please email us with the new information or your review request at [info@billmatrix.com](mailto:info@billmatrix.com). We will make every reasonable effort to make sure your requests are honored.

Computer Tracking and Cookies   
Our website is not set up to track, collect or distribute personal information not entered by its visitors. Our website logs do generate certain kinds of non-identifying site usage data, such as the number of hits and visits to our site. This information is used for internal purposes by technical support staff to provide better services to our customers and may also be provided to others.

Outside Links   
Our website may contain links to and from other websites. We are not responsible for their privacy practices and encourage you to investigate the privacy practices of those websites.

Problems   
If you have a question about our privacy policy, you may contact us at [info@billmatrix.com](mailto:info@billmatrix.com).
